const QUESTIONS_DEF = [
  {
    question: "What attribute is used in the '<script>' tag to link to a Javascript file?",
    answers: ["src", "href", "a", "aria"]
  },
  {
    question: "Who created Javascript while working for Netscape in 1995?",
    answers: ["Brandon Eich", "Bjarne Stroustrup", "James Gosling", "Tim Berners-Lee"]
  },
  {
    question: "What pair of symbols follows the end of a function?",
    answers: ["()", "[]", "{}", "<>"]
  },
  {
    question: "What's the main difference in how '===' and '==' compare values?",
    answers: ["type", "int", "assignment", "iteration"]
  },
  {
    question: "What data type is to be expected in the parenthesis after a 'while' loop?",
    answers: ["boolean", "integer", "string", "object"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a correct implementation of a 'for' loop?",
    answers: ["for (var i = 0; i <= 10; i++) { ... }", "for (i > 10) { ... }", "for (var i = 0; i == true ; i++) { ... }", "for (i + i * 10) { ... }"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a correct implementation of a single-line comment in Javascript?",
    answers: ["// comment", "/ comment /", "/- comment -/", "/-/ comment /-/"]
  },
  {
    question: "What pair of symbols is used to denote an array?",
    answers: ["[]", "()", "{}", "<>"]
  },
  {
    question: "What will 'Math.random()' return?",
    answers: ["a floating value between 0 and 1", "undefined", "an integer between 1 and 10", "an integer between 0 and 9"]
  },
  {
    question: "What company currently owns the rights to Javascript?",
    answers: ["Oracle", "Google", "International Organization for Standardization", "Microsoft"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a variable keyword in Javascript?",
    answers: ["int", "var", "let", "const"]
  },
  {
    question: "What operator is used to perform multiplication?",
    answers: ["*", "x", "#", "multiply()"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which one of these statements is correct?",
    answers: ["Javascript is case-sensitive and ignores whitespace", "Javascript is not case-sensitive and ignores whitespace", "Javascript is case-sensitive and doesn't ignore whitespace", "Javascript is not case-sensitive and doesn't ignore whitespace"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these statements is correct?",
    answers: ["Javascript is a weakly and dynamically typed language", "Javascript is a strongly and dynamically typed language", "Javascript is a weakly and non-dynamically typed language", "Javascript is a strongly and non-dynamically typed language"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which function returns the character at a specified index?",
    answers: ["charAt()", "indexOf()", "getChar()", "getIndex()"]
  },
  {
    question: "Is Javascript multi-threaded?",
    answers: ["no", "yes", "maybe", "so"]
  },
  {
    question: "Is 'null' an object?",
    answers: ["yes", "no", "maybe", "so"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a Javascript file extension?",
    answers: [".js", ".jvs", ".javascript", ".ajt"]
  },
  {
    question: "What Javascript function is used to get an HTML DOM element with a specified ID?",
    answers: ["getElementByID()", "getElement()", "id()", "retrieveElement()"]
  },
  {
    question: "if/else and switch/case are both conditional statements. What is the if/else equivalent of 'default:'?",
    answers: ["else", "break", "continue", "boolean"]
  }
];
